[{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What to do if any virus attacks the rice?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"MD. Shalim Sadman","answer":"The four most important strategies for rice disease management are to rotate crops, plant resistant varieties, plant in warm soil and use fungicides when necessary. An integrated approach that uses all of these methods is the most effective and profitable."},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What is soil health?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"MD. Shalim Sadman","answer":"Soil health is defined as the continued capacity of soil to function as a vital living ecosystem that sustains plants, animals, and humans."},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"MD. Shalim Sadman","answer":"The most commonly used insecticides are the organophosphates, pyrethroids and carbamates"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What is soil health?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Charlie Puth","answer":"Healthy soil gives us clean air and water, bountiful crops and forests, productive grazing lands, diverse wildlife, and beautiful landscapes."},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"Boric Acid, Malathion, Carbaryl"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"Boric Acid, Malathion, Carbaryl"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"for more, visit farmers.gov "},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"for more, visit farmers.gov "},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What are the common insecticides?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"for more, visit farmers.gov "},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What to do if any virus attacks the rice?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"for more, visit farmers.gov"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What is soil health?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"Faiza Karima","answer":"it is a critical concept"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What to do if any virus attacks the rice?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"MD. Shalim Sadman","answer":"It is a very difficult topic"},{"question":"<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>\r\n<note>\r\n<q1>What to do if any virus attacks the rice?<\/q1>\r\n<topic>(agriculture)<\/topic>\r\n\r\n<\/note>","user":"MD. Shalim Sadman","answer":"Use pestricides"}]